currenthiphop.com 2014-05-17

# CurrentHipHop.com - Stream and download the latest hip-hop music

Open Road, LLC, a Delaware Limited Liability Company ("the Company", “we”, “our” or “us”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the website located at http://www.currenthiphop.com (“Currenthiphop” or the "Site"), you are accepting the practices outlined in this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”).

The terms "You" and "Your" refer to you, as a user of the Site. The terms "Personal Information" and "Your Information" mean information that personally identifies you or allows you to be contacted or identified, such as your username, email address, and any other data that is tied to such information.

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers treatment of Personal Information that you provide to us and that we gather when you are on the Site. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our business partners may share with us.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that the Company does not own or control, or to individuals that the Company does not employ or manage.

What Information About Customers Does Currenthiphop Collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized and efficient experience while on the Site. We collect the following types of information from our users:

Information You Provide to Us

We receive and store any information you enter on the Site or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our Site's features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to requests for certain services, customizing the content and advertising, and communicating with you about specials, new products, services and features. In order for you to use our Site, you are not required to register; however, you must register to take advantage of certain features of the Site, such as bookmarking favorites and other information to appear on your dashboard, and receiving e-mail newsletters from us. To register, you must provide your e-mail address, a username and a password. 

Information Collected Automatically

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with the Site. The Company automatically receives and records traffic data on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the webpage you requested. The Company uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its server, analyze trends and administer the Site.

Generally, we automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular television show. This data is only used in the aggregate and not in a way that would identify you personally, and enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Site. In addition, we may provide statistical information, not information about you personally, to our partners about how our users, collectively, use our Site. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how people use the Site, so that they may provide you with an optimal online experience.

E-mail Communications

We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from Currenthiphop if your computer supports this type of program. We do this in order to help us make e-mails more interesting and helpful and to improve our service. We also send out e-mails with news or promotions. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please contact us at [email@currenthiphop.com].

Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that the Site transfers to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when webpages in our Site are visited and by how many people. Currenthiphop cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us what your username or e-mail address is or who you are.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will either prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie or fully disable cookies. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Currenthiphop's most attractive features.

The following advertising agencies, advertising networks and other companies (collectively, "Advertisers") place advertisements on the Site and may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technology to collect information about users. The Company does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and we have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. Click on the links to learn more about their practices and the choices they provide you:

  1. [Vibe Media/Access Network Privacy Policy](http://www.vibe.com/page/privacy-policy)

Will the Company Share Any of the Information it Receives?

Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below.

Affiliated Business We Do Not Control. The Company is affiliated with other businesses and works closely with them. We may provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses through the Site. We may share customer information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business as necessary. We require our affiliates to provide the same level of privacy protection that we do and they do not have the right to share or use Personal Information for any purpose other than for an authorized transaction.

Agents. We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. Our agents subscribe to the same level of privacy protection as we do. Unless we tell you differently, the Company’s agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us.

Protection of the Company and Others. We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Company, our employees, our users or others. This includes, without limitation, exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. The Company may disclose Personal Information to parties in compliance with our Copyright Policy, as the Company in its sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity. In such events, the Company may disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, e-mail address and company name.

With Your Consent. Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties.

Is Information About Me Secure?

Your Currenthiphop account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure there is no unauthorized access to your password and to your account by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

The Company strives to protect user information to make sure that it is kept private. However, we cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

What Information Can I Access?

Currenthiphop allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. This list may change as the Site changes.

  1. Username and password
  2. Email address

You are able to add or update certain information. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain Currenthiphop features.

You may request deletion of your Currenthiphop account by sending an email to [support@currenthiphop.com]. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please e-mail us at [support@currenthiphop.com]. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Site, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

Can Children Use Currenthiphop's Services?

Currenthiphop is not intended for children. If you are under 18, you may use the Site only under supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under 13 years of age, you are not allowed to register for or use Currenthiphop. We never knowingly collect Personal Information from persons under the age of 13. If we learn that we have any information or content from anyone under the age of 13, we will take commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information in a timely manner.

Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit the Site, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes and application of New York state law.

Third Party Sites

The Site provides links to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Site. These other websites are not under the Company’s control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and the Company is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

The Company may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Site so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.

Loading...
